automotivecraze.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

Automotive Craze understands the concerns people have about privacy and safety while using the Internet. This Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from visitors, how we use that information, and the steps we take to protect your privacy.

  1. Automotive Craze collects information from visitors through voluntary site registration, voluntary submission of information when purchasing products or completing an online employment application, and through the voluntary acceptance of cookies. Automotive Craze will not collect information from you if you do not want us to collect it.
  2. Automotive Craze uses cookies (small pieces of code delivered to visitors’ systems) to learn more about the way in which people use our site. We do not perform any individual analysis of this data and are not interested in individual information. Cookies allow us to tell what type of browsers our audience uses, which helps us to design our site so that everyone can access it. We also find out how people are using our site (what parts of the site get viewed more than others), which helps us make better content and layout decisions.
  3. Automotive Craze uses a secure firewall to keep out unauthorized users and ensure the integrity of our systems. We are vigilant about protecting our site from unwanted intrusions.
  4. Automotive Craze does not sell, trade, or otherwise release any personal information on our site visitors or subscribers. We respect your desire for privacy and zealously protect any information you give us. Your information is safe with us!
  5. We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

If you have any questions at all about our Privacy Policy or our Web site, [ please send us a message](mailto:admin@automotivecraze.com).  
Thank you for visiting our site.
